<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>z13o</title>
    <link href="https://z13o.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://z13o.com" />
    <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>The Author</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://z13o.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Heptabase | A Note-Taking Tool To Make Sense of Complex Topics</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/heptabase-or-a-note-taking-tool-to-make-sense-of-complex-topics.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/heptabase-or-a-note-taking-tool-to-make-sense-of-complex-topics.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/1-3-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Startups"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/1-3-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    Heptabase focuses on visually presenting a full knowledge base while allowing for granular details even at a large scale. First thought, this opens up opportunities to training and knowledge transfer in methods other than a list of book marks in a Slack channel or pointing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/1-3-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Heptabase focuses on visually presenting a full knowledge base while allowing for granular details even at a large scale. First thought, this opens up opportunities to training and knowledge transfer in methods other than a list of book marks in a Slack channel or pointing someone at a Confluence board. </p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The second thought we had while reviewing Heptabase is the possibility it has to support Memory Palace styles of data organization. The market has a lot of "note taking" products currently, however only a few teams are reinventing how the data is visualized (not to be confused with organization). The top 5 note taking apps you can think of have a left side bar for note or page names and a center section for content. Heptabase diverges from the standard market model so much it feels like a new product.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"id":948,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figure class="wp-image-948"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/1-3-1024x469.jpg" alt="woman teaching a boy"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/responsive/1-3-1024x469-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/responsive/1-3-1024x469-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/responsive/1-3-1024x469-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/responsive/1-3-1024x469-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/responsive/1-3-1024x469-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/24/responsive/1-3-1024x469-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Currently Heptabase is a manual or semi manual process for creating and editing documentation, however there is a real value here in generating documentation from Git or Jira data sources to offer a backwards compatible service. Imagine if all the documentation you wish you had for internal products was programmatically solvable by a ML service that imported it into a Heptabase? It would be documentation for technical debit organized in an easy to read and learn visual learning tool.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Starting a customer base is always harder than borrowing your competitors. In our opinion, integrations with current market heavy weights like GitHub or Jira would allow for easier opt-in customer acquisitions. The product is differentiated enough in concept to not get an apples to apples comparison from early adopters and could lead to better brand recognition.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5><strong>Market</strong></h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Heptabase has a possible seat in-between the Office Productivity and Software Development Tools sectors, as both markets could leverage such a tool. Currently Google and Microsoft are dominating Office Productivity with companies like Evernote winning in smaller sectors of the market. Software Development Tools is a more fractured market with many solutions not fully over lapping on services. Most of the Software Development Tools require heavy API integrations to stay competitive since the market is a landing point for breakout data from the Software Configuration Management market. Software Configuration Management is dominated by GitHub, GitLab, and others. Software tools as a whole is estimated to reach $158B globally in 2022.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Visit their <a href="https://heptabase.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" title="website">website</a> to learn more. </p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>NFT Scoring</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/nft-scoring.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/nft-scoring.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/25/Capture.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="Startups"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/25/Capture.png" alt="" />
                    NFT Analytics PlatformFind promising NFT projects via AI This is an obvious win in todays NFT gold rush. In the original west coast gold rush the people selling the tools were ultimately the most successful. With this example in mind, NFT Scoring would be the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/25/Capture.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>NFT Analytics PlatformFind promising NFT projects via AI</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5><strong>Thoughts</strong></h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>This is an obvious win in todays NFT gold rush. In the original west coast gold rush the people selling the tools were ultimately the most successful. With this example in mind, NFT Scoring would be the people setting the price of gold and tracking its supply. They are competing in a marketplace that already has major players like OpenSea but due to the easy access of information at the NFT Scoring website it lends to break in opportunities.<br>It would be good to read <a href="https://www.z13o.com/post/ethereum-erc721" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">THIS </a>post to understand this next point better. Currently most NFTs are off block chain assets linked in a URL in the NFT, calling out which are on and off block would be good to know as it effects the assets longevity and value.<br>This is such a new market it is hard to see what there is to disrupt other than the chaos of a new asset class. If we took a stab at it, we would guess that leveraging the API angle is possibly the strongest long term trajectory. Mobile NFT access is reliant on API access as mobile cannot load a full blockchain to verify if someone owns an NFT and relies on services like this to identify who owns what.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5><strong>Market</strong></h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The NFT sector is projected to reach $35B this year by some early adopters, and move on to 80B in 2025. Due to the lack of historical information on this market it is hard to tell if this is true, but if taken the history of Bitcoin into account it would point towards the market having longevity (not all smooth sailing). Since this is a speculatory market currently and vulnerable to fraud, it is a great market to be in data and not specifically holding off assets.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The 10 Must-Follow Marketing Tips before Launching an App</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/the-10-must-follow-marketing-tips-before-launching-an-app.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/the-10-must-follow-marketing-tips-before-launching-an-app.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/35/1-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Tech"/>
            <category term="Guides"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/35/1-1-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    You have reached the stage where your app is finished developing and is prepared to be released on the market. You've put a lot of effort into getting here, so take some time to figure out what to do before, during, and after your mobile&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/35/1-1-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>You have reached the stage where your app is finished developing and is prepared to be released on the market. You've put a lot of effort into getting here, so take some time to figure out what to do before, during, and after your mobile app launch. In this article, we will share some important tips that will assist you in your pre-launching strategy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>These 10 Marketing tips will help you in your pre-launching strategy</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<p style="font-size:25px"><strong>1) Study your competition</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>A good sports team spends time researching their opponent before any important game. Research on each opponent's player will be done by coaches, who will also view the game tape and compile scouting reports. A competition analysis is a technique for creating a game plan that will help your business prosper, similar to a scouting report for your industry.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Look for similar apps in the google play store and the apple app store, check them out and note their weaknesses and strengths. This will also help you have a better idea of your app.You still have time to alter features or functionalities. Look at their Reviews and Ratings to identify the features that annoy users the most and eliminate them in your app.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It's not about duplicating other apps; it's about making yours as good as you can! Analyze your competitors and profit from their weaknesses!</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<p style="font-size:25px"><strong>2) Define your goals and target audience</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>First and foremost, make sure your product is original before investing your time in designing and developing it. Since there are so many apps available, it can be difficult to outperform your rivals these days. You should have clear goals and a target audience in your mind.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Set realistic goals rather than being overly greedy. You should be targeting your audience as you are identifying and planning your objectives. What features does your product possess, in your opinion? What are its major purposes? Which demographic would benefit from your app or game the most? You should have answers to these questions and market your app accordingly.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<p style="font-size:25px"><strong>3) App Store Optimization</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Getting your app noticed is one of the biggest problems facing mobile app publishers today, with more than 6 million mobile apps available in the major app stores. This is why it's so important to understand app store optimization (ASO).</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Mobile apps are optimized for app stores to appear better in search results. This is known as app store optimization. Potential users will see your app more often the higher it ranks in the search results of an app store. More people frequently visit the app store page for your app as a result of the enhanced visibility.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Don't forget about optimizing for the app store. Your list of priorities should always include app store optimization. ASO assists you in increasing your app visibility in the store, increasing your conversion rate, and generating more organic installs. Before publishing your app, make sure that all of your ASO components (app store listings) are optimized. This will give you an edge over your competitors.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<p style="font-size:25px"><strong>4) Create a Landing Page</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>A landing page is a separate web page designed expressly for a marketing or advertising campaign in digital marketing. It's the page that a visitor "lands" on after clicking on an email link, an advertisement from Google, Bing, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, or another comparable website.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Landing pages are created with a single emphasis or purpose, known as a call to action, as opposed to other web pages, which often have multiple aims and encourage exploration.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Make a landing page and send your target audience there. You can use this landing page to explain the app's features and to advertise your app. With WordPress, Wix, or any other content management system for quickly building websites, you can design your landing page. You can also share this landing page on social media websites like Facebook, Reddit, Twitter e.t.c and get free organic users for your app. This is a very important tip. Share your landing page where your target audience hangs out and share your landing page there.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":3,"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<h3 style="font-size:25px"><strong>5) Pay attention to your Content Marketing Strategy</strong></h3>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The creation and distribution of relevant, useful content such as blogs, newsletters, white papers, social media postings, emails, videos, and similar items—to current and future clients is known as content marketing. When done well, this content demonstrates competence and makes it obvious that a business values the customers it serves.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Using content marketing consistently helps you build and maintain relationships with both current and potential clients. When your target market views your business as a partner invested in their success and a reliable source of information and guidance, they are more likely to choose you when the time comes to make a purchase.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Welcome others to become a part of your community. Try to catch their interest with interesting and compelling content. Create interest in your app and keep it alive by posting interesting content frequently on your blog or social media pages about it.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>You need to consider your target audience once more at this point. Consider what they could be looking for and where they might find it. Along with creating your blog, you may also contact some blogs that currently have traffic that relates to your target audience and exchange guest posts. Draw attention to the features and benefits of your app and include links that will direct readers to your landing page.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<p style="font-size:25px"><strong>6) Use Social Media to your advantage</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>For businesses of all sizes, social media marketing is an effective way to connect with prospects and clients. If you're not using social media sites like Facebook, Instagram, and LinkedIn, you're missing out. Effective social media marketing can help your business achieve extraordinary success by generating loyal supporters, leads, and even purchases.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Start promoting the features and capabilities of your app on various social media platforms. People will be interested in your launch and wait for it because of this. Use the social media channels that your target audience utilizes the most and consistently upload fresh, engaging and unique content.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Sending reminder emails that highlight your launch date can help you generate even more buzz. Try to capture people's interest as much as you can!</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":3,"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<h3 style="font-size:25px"><strong>7) Create a Video Teaser</strong></h3>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Teasers are brief videos with the primary goal of generating buzz. You usually picture teaser videos for movies or songs, however this form of video isn't solely used in the entertainment sector. In reality, teaser videos can play a crucial role in a business's product or service marketing strategy.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Nowadays, the majority of content is created with the audience's wants and needs in mind. Teaser videos are designed to leave viewers hanging. They only provide the audience with enough information to stimulate their interest. People are attracted by effective teaser videos by getting a sneak peek of what will be revealed later. This can give you the upper hand over business rivals that are competing for customers and keep you at the forefront of people's minds.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It's a proven fact that people would rather watch than read. So creating a video is a must. Make a short, straightforward video that highlights the most important features of your app. Grab the attention of the user within the first 5 seconds and you should also include a call to action message. You can use this video to advertise on social media networks. You can create advertisements and specifically target your target audience on social media websites like facebook, reddit e.t.c using the teaser video.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<p style="font-size:25px"><strong>8) Broaden your network</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Join online communities related to your niche on social media sites like Facebook, Reddit, Instagram, and LinkedIn and start networking. Networking is very powerful and can help you achieve massive business success. Provide real value to those online communities. tell them how your app solves problems and the main features of your app.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>As soon as you can, start making new friends, and get in touch with media contacts. Social media followers are significantly influenced by influencers. They may spread the word about your app among their following, which would increase the number of individuals eagerly anticipating your launch.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>You can also contact the social media influencers and work out some kind of promotion deal with them. They will charge you but it can be worth it in the long run. As mentioned above, these influencers have hundreds of thousands of followers. They are very powerful in the social media space. If they can promote your app in their posts, You will get many installs.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<p style="font-size:25px"><strong>9) Make sure you have a neat app</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Before your product's launch, you need input. You have only received input from your team up to this point, but you now need an outside perspective.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Make sure that your app does not have any bugs or glitches. If there are any bugs or glitches, make sure to remove them before launch. If they are not removed then the users will give you bad reviews and ratings on app stores and this can hurt the success of your app. Therefore it is very important for you that you release a clean app, free of bugs and glitches.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Have a few of your target audience members beta-test your app and provide feedback on what should be improved. When your product is eventually launched, be sure to reward them. You can give them access to exclusive content, special features, deals, discounts, or anything else you can think of.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":3,"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<h3 style="font-size:25px"><strong>10) Schedule your launching date</strong></h3>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>We are aware that you would like to release your app on the day that your developers inform you it is complete, but in all honesty, this is not a wise move. You must generate buzz before making your app available in the stores, as we have been advising you throughout this article. Make sure you have enough time to promote your app and make sure the day it launches doesn't coincide with any major industry events.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"25px"}}} --></p>
<h2 style="font-size:25px"><strong>Are you ready to launch your app?</strong></h2>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>In this article, We shared the ten most important marketing tips before launching an app. Implement these before you launch your app. You will have amazing results.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>To sum it up the top 10 marketing tips before launching an app are to study your competition, define your goals and target audience, App Store Optimisation (ASO), Create a landing page, Pay attention to your content marketing strategy, use social media to your advantage, create a video teaser, broaden your network, make sure you have a neat app, schedule your launching date.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 Best No Code Development Platforms</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/5-best-no-code-development-platforms.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/5-best-no-code-development-platforms.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/34/14-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Tech"/>
            <category term="Guides"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/34/14-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    A no-code platform is a programming platform that allows users to build apps without writing any code. It enables non-technical users to build applications by dragging and dropping software applications to create a full app. Users can create applications with no code without having any&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/34/14-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>A no-code platform is a programming platform that allows users to build apps without writing any code. It enables non-technical users to build applications by dragging and dropping software applications to create a full app. Users can create applications with no code without having any prior coding skills. No code platforms are transforming the market right now, which is why they are so popular. I will share the five best no-code development platforms in this article.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The coding industry is being ruled by no code platforms right now. According to the estimates of experts, The global no-code business will grow to $65.15 billion by 2027. No code platforms level the playing field for all users, enabling independent creators, artists, and entrepreneurs to build apps they could previously only have imagined. When it comes to the value offered, when it comes to quick builds, no code platforms are tough to top. Their popularity is likely to continue to grow in the future years as more AI development tools and capabilities are incorporated into no-code platforms. I'll be talking about the most popular no-code platforms nowadays, That you can use.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I'll be highlighting the features and pricing plans.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">What Are The Best No-Code Development Platforms?</h2>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>1) Appy Pie</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Lack of coding experience is no longer a barrier to building apps. Having said that, if you're looking for a fantastic no-code platform for both mobile and software development, I highly recommend checking out Appy Pie.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>One of the top no-code platforms, Appy Pie accelerates mobile app development by 10 times. Regardless of their level of coding expertise, technological proficiency, or budget restrictions, anyone can utilize this platform to create applications.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Additionally, it enables you to drag and drop elements into the application, allowing you to launch the app in a matter of minutes.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Because the platform enables you to make chat boxes, websites, and other things, it will provide your business with an advantage over the competition. Additionally, it aids in the efficient management of tedious tasks through integration and intelligent workflow automation employing triggers and actions.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>You can even connect 300+ apps to simplify tasks and get rid of manual work.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The ability to create eye-catching graphics and images is another important feature of Appy Pie. The images can be used on flyers, posters, websites, business cards, and other materials.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Key Features</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Businesses of all budgets can use Appy Pie. Developing a mobile application has never been so easy. You also don't have to worry about syntax errors and bugs. You just have to pick the right color theme and features and Appy Pie will build the app in minutes.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Most Important Features of Appy Pie</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Friendly and fast customer service</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Connects 300+ apps for free</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Democratizes the creation and development of applications</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>automates processes to increase output</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Create and launch chatbots</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Live chat software</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Custom mobile application development</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>User Experience</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It's incredible how easily one can create a mobile app from scratch.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>A lot of people claim they can make an app in only a few minutes.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The straightforward drag-and-drop user interface is incredibly simple and doesn't require any coding expertise.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Pricing</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Appy pie offers free plans and paid plans. There are three tiers to take into account.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>These are Appy Pie's payment plans, broken down:</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>The basic plan at $16/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Gold plan at $36/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Platinum plan at $60/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Google Play Store charges a one-time fee of $25 while the Apple App Store charges an annual developer fee of $99.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What I Like/Dislike About Appy Pie:</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Like</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>The support staff is always there to assist you with any problems.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>There is no need for coding expertise to use Appy pie, which is incredibly user-friendly.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Dislike</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>It would be useful to include a web view button in the main menu.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Get started with Appy Pie</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>2) ClickUp</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I suggest Clickup if you're seeking a great solution for managing tasks related to project management, documents, and other things. You won't be disappointed, thanks to features that address all needs.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The greatest overall no-code platform for businesses that address a variety of issues is ClickUp. They offer software for project management, tasks, documents, timelines, reminders, collaboration, remote team management, and more. They advertise themselves as "the one app to replace them all."</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>ClickUp is used by over 100,000 well-known companies, including Google, Airbnb, Nike, Netflix, and Uber.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It is a no-code solution that allows users to build custom dashboards for any kind of project, including remote tasks and projects that are ongoing, being reviewed, or being finished.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Along with time management, resource planning that integrates several business units, and numerous tool integrations, ClickUp provides these services.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>In general, ClickUp offers so many use cases that it's challenging to cover them all in one article, including CRM software, project management tools, sales management software, and much more:</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Key Features</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Provides many pre-built templates.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Drag and drop functionality across all tools.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Excellent contact management features.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Allows teams to log their time and goals.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Able to automatically import files from other programs.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Organizes tasks, subtasks, timeframes, and more with ease.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>All without the need for code.&nbsp;</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>User Experience</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The user experience at ClickUp is excellent because everything is so visual.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It's very simple to see what has to be done and when things are due.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I also really appreciate being able to comment on tasks.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>This feature makes it possible for team members to communicate clearly with one another and keeps everyone on the same page.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Pricing</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>ClickUp also provides a free plan that includes 100 MB of storage, unlimited tasks and unlimited members.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Besides the free plan, they also offer:</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li><strong>Unlimited Plan ($5 per user per month): </strong>Adds unlimited dashboards, integrations, views, boards, and lists.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li><strong>Business Plan ($9 per user per month): </strong>Adds all dashboard widgets, private views, goal folders, Google SSO, custom exporting, mind maps, and advanced time tracking.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li><strong>Enterprise (custom pricing):</strong> MSA and HIPAA compliant, increased API limits, a dedicated account manager, all advanced features, white labeling, and custom onboarding and training.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Overall, ClickUp is one of the best no-code development platforms out there. Give it a try, you will not be disappointed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>What I like/Dislike about ClickUp</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Like</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Multiple lists of tasks enable me to stay organized and always know where to search for what I'm looking for.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>I also greatly value how valuable features are consistently added to ClickUp.&nbsp;</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Dislike</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>I don't always know how long I've spent on a task because the time tracking feature is quite basic.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>I also wish there was an admin panel so I could monitor the performance of my entire staff.&nbsp;</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Product Updates</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>ClickUp can now manage more processes without experiencing any lag thanks to improvements in speed and performance. In terms of productivity, this is always a good thing.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The Dashboard filter is also a fantastic feature because it enables you to quickly see the information that matters to you the most.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>3) Airtable</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Airtable is another great no code development platform. There isn't much software on the market that can compete with Airtable's built-in solutions for team and individual organizations.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Data management using Airtable is accessible to every business or marketer. It makes it easier to make databases and spreadsheets with checkboxes, links, attachments, and barcodes. almost functioning as a project management and workflow tool, among many other uses.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The platform allows teams and individuals the flexibility to group, filter, and arrange tasks however they see fit. Even better, it can produce images for many use cases and save them for quick access at any time.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Its 50+ prebuilt apps can be added to the data, and you can connect your integrated workflow for easy management. These apps allow users to collaborate in real-time across all devices thanks to mobile and web-friendly user interface.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>To assist your team in concentrating on what matters, Airtable can automate processes and offer personalized notifications.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Key Features</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Airtable is the perfect tool for all kinds of projects and businesses because of its flexibility. You can design spreadsheets that are as simple or complicated as you need.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>List of features</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Robust API for easy access to content</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Creates project and content calendars</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Data and content management</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Mobile and desktop-friendly</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Built-in integrate tools</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Real-time edits and comments</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>User Experience</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Airtable's user experience is well-liked given the ability to create forms that have a spreadsheet-like appearance and feel.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I love how simple it is to enter data, manipulate it, and produce stunning graphs and charts.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The collaboration features are excellent and make it simple to modify and comment on projects.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Pricing</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>A free plan from Airtable includes limitless bases, each with 1,200 records and 2GB of attachment space. You can upgrade to any of the following paid plans based on the requirements of your team and company.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>1. Plus Plan at $10 Per Seat/Month</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>5GB attachments/base</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>5,000 records/base</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Automatic table syncing with one table per base</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Six-month revision and snapshot history</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>2. Pro Plan at $20 Per Seat/Month</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Unlimited applications</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>20GB attachments/base</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>50,000 records/base</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>One-year revisions and snapshot history</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>3. Enterprise Plan</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Unlimited workspaces/organization</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>1,000 GB attachments/base</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>100,000 records/base</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Three-year revision and snapshot history</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What I Like/Dislike About Airtable:</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Like</strong>:</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Airtable is a superb option for teams because it is an excellent tool for cross-collaboration. The extensive project management toolkit that is included with this is another thing I really value.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Dislike</strong>:</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>There aren't any other themes or layouts available, which can cause projects to look similar.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>4) Kintone</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Teamwork is the key to long term success. I would suggest checking out Kintone if you're seeking a solution that encourages teamwork and collaboration.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The all-in-one, no-code platform for developing applications, Kintone, encourages collaborative working. It assists engineers and software developers in developing powerful applications and databases for their teams and businesses while automating specific workflows.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The platform can create social media calendars for marketing teams, expense reports for accounting teams, and CRM apps for sales teams. This makes it easier for you to see all of your data in one place rather than scattered over twenty different platforms.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>You will receive from Kintone the flexibility of an excel spreadsheet with an added, centralized database. It also provides group collaboration capabilities for tracking, sending, and recalling team discussions. No project communication will ever be lost in your chat or inbox search results.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Key Features:</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The dynamic database offered by Kintone, which can be accessed from any location at any time, will be helpful to business customers who are just starting. Additionally, it offers a range of development tools for different use cases.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>The following is a list of the features Kintone has to offer:</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Workflow and development process automation for data-driven results</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Uninterrupted view of data</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Collaborative tools</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Smooth user experience</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>CRM web apps</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Streamlines business process</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>User Experience:</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>One of Kintone's biggest features is its configurable interface, which enables you to instantly alter the appearance and feel of your app.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>When you first launch the app, you can have widgets for threads, apps, people, and more. You can then move them around to anywhere you like.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>This makes it quite simple to locate what you're looking for and immediately begin working.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pricing:</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Everybody, including startups, governmental agencies, and businesses, can choose from one of Kintone's price options. After determining your ROI by entering the necessary metrics, you can select a plan.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Here are its four payment plans:</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Professional subscription plan at $24/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Enterprise subscription plan (request quote)</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Education and government subscription plan at $15/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Nonprofit subscription plan at $15/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What I Like/Dislike About Kintone:</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Like</strong>:</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Email alerts are fantastic since they let you monitor activity in your app even when you're not using it.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>The support staff is also highly informed and understanding and they are always eager to help with any problems you may encounter.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Dislike</strong>:</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>It would be excellent if there was a smoother transition between tasks.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>The existing GUI could use some aesthetic improvement.</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>5) Bubble</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Bubble guarantees total design freedom to produce dynamic, mobile-friendly content and app layouts. CSS or HTML knowledge is not required.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The platform also manages the hosting of websites and the deployment process. Data storage, traffic volume, and user count are all unrestricted. It offers a scalable foundation for multi-user apps and is completely customizable.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Features:</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>You can use Bubble to present a prototype of your idea. Small enterprises rely on it for web development because of this.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Features offered by Bubble:</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Drag-and-drop editor</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Scalable and secure data storage</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Fully customizable</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Supports prototype demonstration</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pricing:</strong></h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><strong>Here are the pricing plans provided by Bubble:</strong></p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Personal plan at $25/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Professional plan at $115/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list-item --></p>
<li>Production plan at $475/month</li>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<p>
<!-- /wp:list --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How Simone Health Transforms The Lives Of Women</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/how-simone-health-transforms-the-lives-of-women.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/how-simone-health-transforms-the-lives-of-women.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/5-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Startups"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/5-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    Polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) is a hormonal syndrome that occurs in women during their reproductive years. Someone with PCOS, may not have periods very often. Or she may have periods that extends over many days. She may also have too much androgen that may result&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/5-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) is a hormonal syndrome that occurs in women during their reproductive years. Someone with PCOS, may not have periods very often. Or she may have periods that extends over many days. She may also have too much androgen that may result in excess facial and body hair, severe acne, and even male-pattern baldness.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Enter Simone Health, a company helping women living with chronic conditions by providing them with data-driven care and compassionate health instructions.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4>How Simone Health Transform the Lives of Women with PCOS</h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"align":"left","id":780,"sizeSlug":"full","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image alignleft size-full"><figure class="wp-image-780"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/SocialShareImage1200x630-1-1.jpg" alt=""  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/responsive/SocialShareImage1200x630-1-1-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/responsive/SocialShareImage1200x630-1-1-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/responsive/SocialShareImage1200x630-1-1-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/responsive/SocialShareImage1200x630-1-1-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/responsive/SocialShareImage1200x630-1-1-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/29/responsive/SocialShareImage1200x630-1-1-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Simone Health is accessible and affordable psychology-based digital therapeutic and remote screening & monitoring platform for Polycystic Ovary Syndrome.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It currently focuses on the management of PCOS, and offers clinically validated nutrition, exercise, stress and sleep guidance specific to PCOS.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>PCOS Mobile App</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>With it's mobile app, it offers doctor recommended nutrition, exercise, stress and sleep instructions specific to PCOS. It delivers evidence-based, compassionate, and personalized PCOS guidance developed by a team of PCOS professionals, dietitians, and personal trainers.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>You can download the app through <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=co.fighealth.app&hl=en&gl=US" target="_blank" rel="noopener" title="Google Play Store">Google Play Store</a> and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pcos-diet-period-tracker/id1569818948" target="_blank" rel="noopener" title="App Store">App Store</a>.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>PCOS Blood Tests</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Simone Health also provides convenient and relatively affordable at-home PCOS blood tests. This allows the company to gather data to give women a quarterly diagnosis. You don’t have to wait for over 2 years and 3-5 visits to find out your PCOS status.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>These tests are the same ones that fertility clinics and gynecologists use. But when availing the tests directly from Simone Health, you also receive counseling and you spend considerably less.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>PCOS is only the beginning</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>As we speak, Simone Health is looking for ways to be the go-to-platform for women’s metabolic health and target other chronic health conditions that disproportionately affect women of all ages. They are looking to address issues concerning menopause, menstrual dysfunction, postpartum depression, and many more.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>They are collecting a massive amounts of biomarker data. This can hopefully further the research efforts around improving women’s metabolic health.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How Two Dots Make Underwriting Easy and Secure</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/how-two-dots-make-underwriting-easy-and-secure.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/how-two-dots-make-underwriting-easy-and-secure.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/4-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Tech"/>
            <category term="Startups"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/4-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    The United States is the largest tech market in the world, representing 32% of the total, or approximately $1.7 trillion for 2020. The tech sector accounts for a significant portion of economic activity in the country. CompTIA's Cyberstates report reveals that the economic impact of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/4-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The United States is the largest tech market in the world, representing 32% of the total, or approximately $1.7 trillion for 2020. The tech sector accounts for a significant portion of economic activity in the country. CompTIA's Cyberstates report reveals that the economic impact of the U.S. tech sector, measured as a GDP percentage, exceeds that of most other industries, including retail, construction, and transportation.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>This priority in technology makes lives easier for Americans and has produced helpful tools to improve business processes. One example of such a tool is Two Dots.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4>What is Two Dots for?</h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"align":"left","id":776,"sizeSlug":"full","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image alignleft size-full"><figure class="wp-image-776"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/c1804f071195395a7ee4e56441cb6e6f599b6b80.png" alt="Two Dots Logo"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/responsive/c1804f071195395a7ee4e56441cb6e6f599b6b80-xs.png 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/responsive/c1804f071195395a7ee4e56441cb6e6f599b6b80-sm.png 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/responsive/c1804f071195395a7ee4e56441cb6e6f599b6b80-md.png 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/responsive/c1804f071195395a7ee4e56441cb6e6f599b6b80-lg.png 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/responsive/c1804f071195395a7ee4e56441cb6e6f599b6b80-xl.png 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/30/responsive/c1804f071195395a7ee4e56441cb6e6f599b6b80-2xl.png 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Two Dots is a fairer gateway to credit and housing markets. It's takes out the long process of providing the underwriter with many documents as evidence that you can afford a product.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The company is based in New York, United States, and its partners include Y combinator, Pomegranate, Garmoosh, and Velo City.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Henson Orser is the CEO and co-founder of the company. He started his career at Goldman in NYC. And after nearly 4 years, he jumped to the startup world as the 4th employee at Findigs (B2B proptech), where he had a front-row seat to how unoptimized consumer underwriting is.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Alongside him is Max Ponte, the CTO and co-founder. Max started his career as one of the first engineers on the income verification team at Blend. He spent years working on this problem in the mortgage industry before making the jump to work on search at Google. After experiencing the excitement of being early at a rapidly scaling startup and the mega-scale of search at Google, he decided to tackle the gigantic problem of payroll data.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Check out <a href="https://www.zimyo.com/insights/biggest-payroll-challenges-in-2019/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" title="9 Biggest Payroll Challenges in 2022">9 Biggest Payroll Challenges in 2022</a> to learn more.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4>Two Dots' Mission</h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The company's mission is to make all consumer underwriting fairer by enabling seamless payroll data access between companies and consumers.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Two Dots manage income verification in a very efficient way.  A customer who wants to borrow money doesn't have to get into the hassle of looking for documents. It has a fully automated process in which qualified applicants applying for loans have their income approved instantly. Within split seconds, business owners can convert the prospects to tenants ,</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The company also integrates two or more systems for a more streamlined business process. It assures coherent transfer between systems and offers advanced fraud protection for customers and business owners. Two Dots also saves time for financial institutions so they can make faster and smarter underwriting decisions within minutes.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Industries That Are Investing in Artificial Intelligence</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/industries-that-are-investing-in-artificial-intelligence.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/industries-that-are-investing-in-artificial-intelligence.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/7-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Tech"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/7-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    The investment in Artificial Intelligence is dominated by tech giants such as Amazon, Google, Microsoft, and Baidu. Whereas, nearly 10% to 30% of the investment comes from non-tech companies depending upon their respective industry. Such companies play a vital role in AI investment and the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/7-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The investment in Artificial Intelligence is dominated by tech giants such as Amazon, Google, Microsoft, and Baidu. Whereas, nearly 10% to 30% of the investment comes from non-tech companies depending upon their respective industry. Such companies play a vital role in AI investment and the size of the AI market is merely a fraction of its size to grow in a few years.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>A large part of the investment in AI goes to its development and very less of it is committed to the acquisition of technology from other firms. According to McKinsey, a vast portion of AI investment is used internally or as an investment in the form of Research and Development and its infrastructure. 2016 was the year when companies together spent around $34 billion which was mainly their internal organizational spending. Internal corporate funding aggregates to $23 billion which makes up nearly three times the levels of investment in space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Statistics</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"id":853,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figure class="wp-image-853"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/1-8-1024x360.jpg" alt="line graph"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/responsive/1-8-1024x360-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/responsive/1-8-1024x360-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/responsive/1-8-1024x360-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/responsive/1-8-1024x360-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/responsive/1-8-1024x360-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/32/responsive/1-8-1024x360-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>As per the Trantica Research survey, Artificial Intelligence projected revenue will rise from $26 billion in 2021 to $90 billion in 2025. A report published by McKinsey on the components of Artificial Intelligence investment highlighted five key areas such as machine learning, computer vision, autonomous vehicles, smart robotics, and virtual agents with their shares of 62%, 31%, 4%, 2%, and 2% respectively.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Several key industries are at the forefront of AI adoption. AI entrepreneur and investor, Bradford Cross pointed out two crucial factors in the businesses such as high profitability and high market capitalization to target them for the adoption of Artificial Intelligence in the initial phase. In another survey conducted by McKinsey, a total of 3000 executives about the adoption of AI applications. Analysis of results showed nearly 32% adoption in the technology and communications sector followed by automotive & assembly and financial services with 29% and 28% respectively.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Demand</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Tencent, the Chinese tech giant, estimates that the number of AI engineers around the globe is 300,000 which appears to be a very low number keeping in view the growing demand and as a result of this shortage people are very difficult to find and those hired are paid high salaries. This seems to suggest a vast majority of students are to be trained in the next few years as the field of artificial intelligence is most likely to create a large number of jobs around the world to be part of the much-valued AI workforce. Only big players that are profitable in the industry are in a better position to hire a workforce for AI. New York times suggests that fresh graduates in the field of AI are hired for around $300,000 to $500,000 on average.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Artificial Intelligence is hard to fill as there is a great demand and it increases by the day. According to Indeed, which is a leading job platform the average number of days to fill an Artificial Intelligence job was up by a staggering period of 60 days. The demand for AI-related jobs included Computer scientists, Algorithm engineers, Principal Scientists, Computer Vision Engineers, Machine Learning Engineers, and Data Scientists. In the same report, it was surveyed that the areas in the US having AI jobs were New York with 12%, San Francisco with 9%, Washington with 8% followed by Boston, Seattle, and Chicago.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Check out <a href="https://www.bestcolleges.com/bootcamps/guides/how-to-learn-ai/#:~:text=You%20can%20learn%20artificial%20intelligence,the%20AI%20to%20learn%20faster." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" title="How to Learn Artificial Intelligence (AI)">How to Learn Artificial Intelligence (AI)</a> to learn more.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Conclusion</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Financing AI has been dominated by technology seeing a good return on investment for companies who aspire to become leaders in the realm of Artificial Intelligence. The financial services sector has been able to pick up AI talent quickly due to their healthy margins. However, for financial services companies and financial services companies, it is a matter of time to see whether they will be leading in the investment in the AI industry or will be knocked out by the tech companies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Flock Homes | Exchange your rental property for shares in a portfolio</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/flock-homes-or-exchange-your-rental-property-for-shares-in-a-portfolio.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/flock-homes-or-exchange-your-rental-property-for-shares-in-a-portfolio.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/8-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Tech"/>
            <category term="Startups"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/8-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    Investing in real estate digitally is on the rise, and it’s giving investors (and would-be investors) more options than ever. Crowdfunded deals (also known as real estate syndication) reached an all-time high after the pandemic, representing $15 billion in 2020 (up from $7 billion in&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/8-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Investing in real estate digitally is on the rise, and it’s giving investors (and would-be investors) more options than ever. Crowdfunded deals (also known as real estate syndication) reached an all-time high after the pandemic, representing $15 billion in 2020 (up from $7 billion in 2019). Notably, this was for online syndications — not necessarily traditional, offline syndications. Offline syndications dropped by 15% in 2020, while online syndications increased. And it doesn’t show signs of slowing down. The real estate crowdfunding market is estimated to increase at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 58.3% from 2020 to 2027.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4>What is Flock Homes?</h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"align":"left","id":823,"sizeSlug":"full","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image alignleft size-full"><figure class="wp-image-823"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/tj9s7c3ndojnzefjtrym.webp" alt="Flock logo"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/responsive/tj9s7c3ndojnzefjtrym-xs.webp 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/responsive/tj9s7c3ndojnzefjtrym-sm.webp 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/responsive/tj9s7c3ndojnzefjtrym-md.webp 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/responsive/tj9s7c3ndojnzefjtrym-lg.webp 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/responsive/tj9s7c3ndojnzefjtrym-xl.webp 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/31/responsive/tj9s7c3ndojnzefjtrym-2xl.webp 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Flock Homes converts individual rental properties into fully-passive, diversified shares in a pool of houses. It helps rental property owners retire from being landlords. The company offers a low-cost, tax-advantaged, hassle-free way to get and keep all the benefits of owning rental properties without any of the burdens. The company was founded in 2020 and is headquartered in Denver, Colorado. They are currently active in Colorado, Kansas, Missouri, North Carolina, Texas, and Washington.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>They are on the mission to create a long-running way to possess homes aiming to provide better financial freedom to the owner, preferred living for inhabitants, and better value to the community. The company is backed by Andreessen Horowitz, Human Capital, 1Sharpe, Redwood Trust, Primary Ventures, and Susa Ventures. They currently accept Single Family Rentals (including duplexes, triplexes, and fourplexes) in Colorado, Kansas, Missouri, North Carolina, Texas, and Washington. </p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Flock distributes the portfolio’s net operating cash flow after accounting for factors such as expenses, debt service, management fees, and capital expenditures every quarter. Flock owners can elect to receive distributions or have distributions reinvested. It targets a 3.0% annual cash distribution yield. Also, it charges a 1% asset management fee and an onboarding fee, comparable to the cost of a traditional sale. The sale of any shares will be treated as the sale of any property, meaning regular capital gains and depreciation recapture taxes apply. One of the benefits of joining Flock is the ability to spread out tax liabilities across years, which could result in lower costs over time.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":4} --></p>
<h4>Generate best returns</h4>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Let the company know about the property and they sought to give one a final offer in 24 hours. If one accepts the offer then flockhomes will take ownership of the property and will receive the shares in their managed portfolios without triggering taxes. One can get a chance to relax and enjoy the benefits of passive income, diversification, and deferred taxes. Depending on how long one has owned the property, selling could lead to the loss of nearly 1/3 of the value to taxes, fees, and lost months’ rental income. </p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Joining Flock allows one to avoid the taxes and hassles associated with a traditional sale. It holds title to the houses in the portfolio and operates like a long-term owner: they've incentivized to generate the best returns for their owners, deliver their residents the best experience, and act in a way that is consistent with the long-term interests of the community and environment. Flock is excited to be a long-term owner of every property that joins the portfolio. That being said, their fiduciary duty is to generate the best returns for the portfolio, and they will strategically cull the portfolio if an attractive opportunity presents itself.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Fisher investments and FlockHomes have Unlike many money managers who sell cookie-cutter portfolios, they tailor portfolios according to everybody's needs and demands by a deep understanding of one's situation, goals, and needs. Both the companies don’t sell high-commission investment products and earn no commissions on trades. They charge one simple, straightforward fee.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Visit their website <a href="https://flockhomes.com/https://flockhomes.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" title="here">here</a>.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 Easy-to-download Apps Every Startup Has To Have</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/5-easy-to-download-apps-every-startup-has-to-have.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/5-easy-to-download-apps-every-startup-has-to-have.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/9-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Tech"/>
            <category term="Startups"/>
            <category term="Guides"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/9-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    In this article, we are sharing the five most essential apps that every startup needs. These apps will increase the productivity and efficiency of your business. A productivity suite includes a business email account, cloud storage and productivity tools. These are the most basic and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/9-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>In this article, we are sharing the five most essential apps that every startup needs. These apps will increase the productivity and efficiency of your business.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"id":825,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figure class="wp-image-825"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/1-2-1024x436.jpg" alt="mobile apps on the phone"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/responsive/1-2-1024x436-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/responsive/1-2-1024x436-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/responsive/1-2-1024x436-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/responsive/1-2-1024x436-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/responsive/1-2-1024x436-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/33/responsive/1-2-1024x436-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>A productivity suite</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>A productivity suite includes a business email account, cloud storage and productivity tools. These are the most basic and essential tools you need for your business. The most popular and widely used productivity suites are Microsoft 365 and Google workspace. Both of these are industry-leading productivity suites. You can go with either one of these</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Graphic design app</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>To develop a strong brand identity, you will need to design great quality visuals for your business. A graphic design app will take care of this.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>These visuals include logos and other business visuals. Canva is the best graphic design app available right now. It will give you access to thousands of customizable design templates, stock photos, royalty-free videos, graphics and much more. Canva has a free version and a paid version. The paid version will unlock over 600,000 templates. However, its free version is quite good too and has many features.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Website or online store</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>There are many website-building platforms available these days. You need to choose the right option although it might be difficult. We have made making that choice easier for you. If your website is not selling any products or services then you can go for square space because of its reasonable pricing. It's very easy to create a website with square space because of its drag and drop elements to create and modify web pages. There are many attractive templates to choose from. Their customer service is also good and will help you out with any problem you face.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Another option is WordPress. It's a free and open-source content management system. However, building a website with WordPress requires a bit more technical knowledge. You can consider hiring a web developer if you want to go with WordPress.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Check out <a href="https://www.dreamhost.com/blog/learn-wordpress/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" title="Want to Learn WordPress? Start with These Resources">Want to Learn WordPress? Start with These Resources</a> to learn more.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Now let's talk about what you should go for if you are building an online store. Many beginners just embed a PayPal button on their web pages to handle financial transactions but that is not the right way to do it. You will need a fully functional store and a platform that will allow you to build that store. Big commerce and Shopify are the big names in this space. They are packed with tons of features to help you build your dream store.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>An Email Marketing Tool</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Email marketing is very powerful. It can provide a fantastic return on investment. E-newsletters are also a great way to share content with your audience. Doing this will not only build great brand awareness but also improve your SEO.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>E-newsletter apps with free plans are Getresponse and Aweber. Many online business owners undermine email marketing. This approach is a big mistake. If done right, email marketing can do wonders for your business. Our favourite app for email marketing is Getresponse because of its cheap pricing and reliability.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>CRM</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>CRM is customer relationship management. It refers to cloud-based software that allows business owners to track and manage the relationship with their leads and clients. A CRM app will allow you to organize leads, track communication with leads and clients, allocate tasks to your team, manage your sales pipeline and manage customer inquiries. One effective CRM app that you can use for your business is Hubspot. It comes with a very functional free version. Other options with reasonable pricing are Capsule and Nimble.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How To Compete With Giants</title>
        <author>
            <name>The Author</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://z13o.com/how-to-compete-with-giants.html"/>
        <id>https://z13o.com/how-to-compete-with-giants.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/3-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Guides"/>

        <updated>2023-07-20T12:40:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/3-1-scaled.jpg" alt="" />
                    Competition is not only restricted to other startups. Brands and big-name giants like Amazon and Google make life tough for startup companies as they must compete with large-scale competitors with bigger budgets and influence. The sheer size and visibility of these major corporations can make&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/3-1-scaled.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Competition is not only restricted to other startups. </p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Brands and big-name giants like Amazon and Google make life tough for startup companies as they must compete with large-scale competitors with bigger budgets and influence. The sheer size and visibility of these major corporations can make it difficult for small businesses to succeed.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>But, while it may seem like you're fighting an uphill battle, achieving success is not impossible. In this article, we talk about the 5 ways to compete with big companies for startup success.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<h2>Listen</h2>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"id":757,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figure class="wp-image-757"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/1-1024x436.jpg" alt="Understand data from customer and competitors"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/1-1024x436-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/1-1024x436-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/1-1024x436-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/1-1024x436-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/1-1024x436-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/1-1024x436-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Customers</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Larger companies can be surprisingly tone-deaf and may not know (or care about) what their customers want. They often have products they won't improve even if their clients beg them to do so. As a small business, you may want to do the opposite. Be obsessed with pleasing the clients. Be sure to listen to what they're asking from you.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>They have their tastes and opinions and will tell you what they want and need. All you have to do is make it happen for them. Clients love businesses that are professional, dedicated, and reliable.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>However, there are times when customer demands can be unrealistic.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Henry Ford said, "If I had asked my customers what they wanted, they would have told me a faster horse." Many times, they don't know what they want except something better, faster, and cheaper.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Competition</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>This is when listening to competitors will help you the most. It is through competitive activities that the market can tell you what your customers won't or don't know yet. Competitive analysis can help you gain knowledge about your competitor's tactics and find opportunities in which you can beat them.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Reading customer reviews, for instance, tells you where your competitors are lacking, which you can use to build a better product.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Competitive analysis is a great way to keep up with industry changes and ensure your product always meets the most recent industry standards. It helps you identify what makes your product stand out from the rest, which informs future marketing.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Check out <a href="https://blog.hubspot.com/marketing/competitive-analysis-kit" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" title="What's a Competitive Analysis & How Do You Conduct One?">What's a Competitive Analysis & How Do You Conduct One?</a> to learn more.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<h2>Be fast</h2>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"id":758,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figure class="wp-image-758"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/2-1024x436.jpg" alt="Team of quick-witted employees"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/2-1024x436-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/2-1024x436-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/2-1024x436-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/2-1024x436-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/2-1024x436-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/2-1024x436-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Big bureaucracy = SLOW</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Ravin Gandhi of GMM Nonstick Coatings said, "Sure, big companies have big resources. But you know what else they have? Big bureaucracy. In other words, they are slow. And if there's something clients hate, it's slow service."</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Fast-emerging startups require a certain level of speed to be successful. Without this requirement, ultimate failure is inevitable. Businesses are constantly coming and going. There are more than half a million start each month, but around 90% fail.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Regardless of how well-funded you are, success eventually requires a lot of dedication and hard work. In the startup world, only those that are persistent and quick will take the cake.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Culture of lightning-fast speed</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Build your company with a culture of lightning-fast speed. Ensure deliverables are sent out within days instead of months and emails are responded to within minutes. You also have to create a team of exceptional employees empowered to make intelligent decisions on the spot.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Big companies are not known for being particularly speedy, so use this to your advantage as you develop your company's system and processes.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Check out <a href="https://tanveernaseer.com/ten-ways-to-speed-up-business-processes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" title="Ten Ways To Speed Up Business Processes">Ten Ways To Speed Up Business Processes</a> to learn more.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<h2>Do not be intimidated</h2>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"id":759,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figure class="wp-image-759"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/3-1024x436.jpg" alt="Man venturing out to the world"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/3-1024x436-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/3-1024x436-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/3-1024x436-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/3-1024x436-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/3-1024x436-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/3-1024x436-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>What motivates you?</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Many people thrive off the feeling of being threatened by competitors. The fear can be both debilitating and motivating, reminding you that your strategic foothold can be lost at any moment.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>In entrepreneurship, this is also the case. The scope and influence of startups seem tiny compared to big corporations, which can be intimidating.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Adam Witty, the founder and CEO of Forbes Books, said, "Certainly, major corporations have plenty of advantages over startups, from the assets they have available to the years of brand recognition they have worked to achieve." It's the harsh reality.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>But that doesn't mean it's over for you.&nbsp;</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>There's no need to throw in the towel just because your competition may be wealthier and more influential.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>As an entrepreneur, you're under a lot of pressure - not just because of the people orbiting you who rely on you to succeed, but mostly because proving it to yourself means the world. Your family and friends are rooting for your idea and waiting for news about it. This pressure fuels the feeling of being intimidated by competitors, especially large companies.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>So what you have to do is to shift your focus to your goals.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>In entrepreneurship, a lot of detail needs to be considered and processes put into place. An easy way to start is by determining the company's overall mission statement. From there, you can establish smaller, more easily achievable goals that will contribute to your eventual mission.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Breaking down the company's mission into smaller, achievable goals will help you understand where your efforts should be focused on.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<h2>Stop psyching yourself out</h2>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"id":760,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figure class="wp-image-760"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/4-1024x436.jpg" alt="Competition is more like a poker than football"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/4-1024x436-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/4-1024x436-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/4-1024x436-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/4-1024x436-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/4-1024x436-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/4-1024x436-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Folks like psyching themselves out</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Founders are easy to assume that their competitors are going to win. It's so easy to think that when you are having a bad time and everyone else is having a great time. You constantly feel like you are failing because you handle the business and have a 360 view of problems and potential ones every day.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It is always good to keep an eye on what companies in the same industry are doing, but it's important not to obsess over them. This could ultimately have you focusing too hard on trying to beat them instead of serving your customers and maintaining your own company.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>A leader's job is to identify when the company or individual has become unclear about how or where to go next and help them remember what is important. This often entails letting go of some of the general insecurities you've picked up as a leader.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Poker not football</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>As Damon Brown, founder of Cuddlr, questions, "Do you really want to set your five-year plan based on what a competitor is doing?" You never know what might happen to your competition. If one of them were to go out of business or pivot, you might have to re-strategize and quickly reallocate resources.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Competition-based pacing might work at the start (in a finite and limited situation), but it doesn't work in the long run. Running a startup is less like football and more like poker. In football, there is one clear opponent. But in poker, there are many. It's a mistake to focus on one opponent. Because what if you focus on one opponent, but another one unexpectedly wipes you out?</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Playing the game is like a never-ending struggle. Don't forget that if you do beat your archenemy, there will be other enemies that you might need to fight down the line.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<h2>Have objectively better products</h2>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:image {"id":761,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figure class="wp-image-761"><img loading="lazy" src="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/5-1024x436.jpg" alt="Have better performing propducts"  sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/5-1024x436-xs.jpg 300w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/5-1024x436-sm.jpg 480w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/5-1024x436-md.jpg 768w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/5-1024x436-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/5-1024x436-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://z13o.com/media/posts/36/responsive/5-1024x436-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure></figure>
<p>
<!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It goes without saying that you need a great product to build a successful startup. While marketers and PR experts often believe they will be able to sell any product through marketing, in reality, a good quality product speaks for itself. No matter how compelling the storytelling is, if a product doesn't deliver strong results, it's all been for nothing.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>"Building great products is a difficult skill, " Avid Larizadeh, COO of Boticca, said.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Many people think that because they have used and have an opinion about products, they could also build one. Product innovators, however, are in short supply. It's also unfortunate that there is no formalized training to become one.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Product people aren't born with their skills - they learn through trial and error and keep learning as time progresses. The most successful ones have years of experience that let them know what works and doesn't. Their passion led them to better understand a great user experience and use the latest tools and technologies to cater to user demands.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>To be just like them, learn how to spot a market gap.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading {"level":5} --></p>
<h5>Spot a market gap</h5>
<p>
<!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>If you're aware of the latest trends, think about what's currently missing from the market. Are there products that customers are willing to buy but no one has made yet? What are the problems of customers you can address? Boiling a market gap down to its very essence, you get an answer to a dilemma that's not currently being solved. It is an opportunity to create a better product.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>It's tough, but you get such an advantage by delivering more value to your end users than everyone else. It's the club you can bludgeon everyone else with.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>So if there's one thing you can take away from this, it is this: just build a better product. When done so, all the other advantages become moot points.</p>
<p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
